

CONTACTS

Minsk, Belarus

+375(29)6737963

anastassia4802

kavgorenya_a@tut.by

in nastassia_kavgorenya

KauhareniaNastassia

% KauhareniaNastassia

Portfolio

LANGUAGES

English B1 (in progress)

Belarusian Native Russian Native

SKILLS

React/Redux

JavaScript

Typescript

HTML/CSS

TDD/Storybook

Axios/Rest API

Thunk

React Hooks

Git/GitHub

Jira

Confluence

Figma

Miro

Nastassia Kauharenia

Front-end developer

ABOUT ME

I am a front-end developer with huge interest in programming. I have an experience in creating SPA with React/Redux/ TypeScript in team. Now I am improving my skills in this direction and expanding them with new technologies, for example, I'm planning to learn Angular. I also have an experience in design, I was studing UX/UI design.

I spend my leisure time reading literature and articles about development, watching video tutorials on YouTube about React and JS.

Open for your suggestions.

EXPERIENCE

May 2022 - present

My projects as front-end developer (Part time)

Library

Stack: React, Redux, Typescript, Redux-Thunk, React-Router-dom, Axios, MUI, SASS, Storybook, Formik, LocalStorage.

Created project with using git, react hooks, routing and redirects, bug fixing.

Cards

Stack: React, Redux, Typescript, Redux-Thunk, React-Router-dom, Axios, MUI, CSS, Formic; Created learning app in team with using git, worked with Axios(CRUD), bug fixing.

Social Network

Stack: React, Redux, Redux-Toolkit, Redux-Thunk, React-Router-dom, Axios, MUI for some components, CSS, SCSS, Formic; Created educational project, organized correct app architecture, bug fixing, refactoring, deploying.

Todolist

Stack: React, Redux, Typescript, Redux-Thunk, React-Router-dom, Axios, MUI, CSS, Storybook, Unit test for some components; Created project with react hooks, routing and redirects, material UI, REST api request/response flow, unit-tests and etc., bug fixing.

June 2019-December 2022

LLC «Сладкое Дело» (Full time)

Lead decorator

- product design
- master classes
- · customer security control
- managing a team of 6 people
- taking part in the development of thematic collections
- training new staff
- monitoring consumables and ordering new ones

EDUCATION

IT-Incubator
Front-end developer
React/Redux/JS/TS

2021-2022

Educational Platform Skillbox
Layout designer
HTML/CSS

IT-school TeachMeSkills

7 - SCHOOL TEACHINGSKIII

UX/UI designer

2011-2015 Belarusian State Economic University

Faculty of Marketing and Logistics

Marketing specialist